Guide to the Malcolm Goldstein Papers MSS.350
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Writing, 263533
  - Subseries C: Correspondence, 265409
    - Nelson, Mark, 2002; 2013; 265536 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Neuhaus, Max, [undated]; 265537 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Nordin, Ingo Loco, [2001-2006]; 265538 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Oja, Carol J. [The College of William and Mary], April 26, 2002; 265539 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Oliveros, Pauline, [1979-1999]; 265540 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Ortenberg, Edgar [Violin Teacher], March 13, 1958; 265541 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Otte, Hans ["Alltagsmusik"], [1990-2006]; 265542 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Paik, Nam June, [undated]; 265543 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Perlis, Vivian [Yale University], October 23, 2003; 265544 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Phillips, Barre, May 31, 2006; January, 2011; 265545 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Piekut, Benjamin - Regarding Charlotte Moorman, February, 2008; 265546 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Rabe, Folke, December 21, 2006; October 9, 2009; 265547 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Reck, David, 1968; [undated]; 265548 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Rothlem, Arlene, [August, 1959]; 265549 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Rudd, Roswell, [1980]; 265550 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Rudhyar, Dan [Tone Roads], March, 1964; 265551 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Rust, Dorothea ["Uber land unter"], [1995-2012][undated]; 265552 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Scelsi, Giacinto, [undated]; 265553 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Schapiro, Meyer, November 19, 1962; 265558 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Schneeman, Carolee, [1988-1995][undated]; 265559 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Schneeman, Carolee ["Cycladic Imprints", "Correspondence Course"], [undated]; 265560 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Schoning, Klaus [WDR: Studio Akustische Kunst], [1984-2004]; 265561 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Schwarzer, Stefan [Musik und Text], March 27, 2003; 265562 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Snow, Michael, August 21, 2001; 265563 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Stiebler, Ernst Albrecht, 2000; 265564 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Suter, Marie ["Winter"], [undated]; 265565 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Tenney, James [1 of 2], [1974-1993][undated]; 265570 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Tenney, James and Eric Smigel [2 of 2], [2007]; 265575 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Thomas, Rudolf [Columbia Composer's Concert], [late 1950's]; 265576 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Ting, Li-Ping ["Fragments of the Wall"], [2002-2004]; 265577 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Varese, Louise, 1976; 265578 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Villars, Chris [Feldman Homages], March 26, 2000; 265579 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Waxman, Donald [Galaxy Music Corporation], August 18, 1975; 265580 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Wiedemann, Carsten [Dancer for "Theater Piece"], December 3, 1996; 265581 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Williams, Christopher ["Jade Mountain Soundings"], November 22, 2011; 265582 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Wilson, Peter Niklaus, [1997-2003][undated]; 265583 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Wolff, Christian ["Bread and Roses"], [1972-1998]; 265589 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Wolpe, Stefan [Music copyist work], [late 1960's]; 265590 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Yates, Peter, December 7, 1965; November 15, 1966; 265591 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Young, Ben [Radio program], September 9, 2003; 265592 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Zinn, Howard, [1996-2005]; 265593 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Series III: Publicity, 265594
  Series III comprises three subseries: Reviews, Photographs, and Ephemera. Each subseries is described more fully below.
  - Subseries A: Reviews, 265595
    Subseries A is comprised of reviews written about Malcolm Goldstein's CD Recordings, Ensemble Pieces, and other performances.
    Folder titles are derived from Malcolm Goldstein's notations and are reflections of his method for categorizing reviews. Each general category of review has been listed alphabetically.
    - After 1990, [2000-2012]; 265596 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - After 1990, [2000-2012]; 265618 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - CD Recordings: "Along the way" Philmuti CD, 2010; 265620 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - CD Recordings: "Chants Caches" Ambiance Magnetique, 1999; 265621 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - CD Recordings: "Christian Wolff: Bread and Roses" Wergo, 2003; 265623 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - CD Recordings: "Early Electronic/ Tape Collage Music" Alga Margen LP, 2008; 265624 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - CD Recordings: "Goldstein plays Goldstein" de capo, 1994; 265626 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - CD Recordings: "Hardscrabble Songs" In Situ, 2004; 265627 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - CD Recordings: "John Cage: Music for violin and percussion" Wergo, 1999; 265628 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - CD Recordings: "Live at Fire in the Valley" Eremite, 1999; 265629 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - CD Recordings: "Monsun" true muze, 1998; 265630 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - CD Recordings: "Pieces from the Past" Pogus [Philip Corner], 2011; 265631 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - CD Recordings: "Portrait Montreal" Quatuor Bozzini, 2004; 265633 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - CD Recordings: "The Seasons: Vermont" XI, 1998; 265635 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - CD Recordings: "The Smell of Light" Nurnichtunur, 2004; 265636 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - CD Recordings: "Soil" Emanen, 2006; 265637 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - CD Recordings: "A Sounding of Sources" New World Recordings, 2008; 265638 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - CD Recordings: "Sounding the New Violin" Non-Sequiter, 1991; 265639 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - CD Recordings: "Speaking in Tongues" Ambiances Magnetiques, 2003; 265640 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Dance Reviews, [1983-1994]; 265641 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Ensemble Pieces [1 of 3], [undated]; 265642 (Box 26, Folder 19)
      Ensemble Pieces include: "Illuminations..." "Tone Roads" "Varese" "A breaking of vessels, becoming song" "Marin's Song, Illuminated" "The Seasons: Vermont" "Cascades of the Brook: Bachwasserfall" "Fiddling Cow Bells" "Horspiel" "Of Sky Bright Mushrooms Bursting In My Head" "Through Deserts of Time"
    - Ensemble Pieces [2 of 3], [undated]; 265643 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Ensemble Pieces [3 of 3], [undated]; 265644 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Other Musicians [1 of 4], [1978-1981]; 265647 (Box 26, Folder 22)
      Includes Reviews of Performances With: Philip Corner and Alison Knowles (first tour of Europe) Joseph Celli and David Moss (with Pauline Oliveros "Witness") Ornette Coleman Festival Matthias Kaul
    - Other Musicians [2 of 4], [1981-1989]; 265648 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Other Musicians [3 of 4], [1980-2009]; 265650 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Other Musicians [4 of 4], [1987-2008]; 265651 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Potluck Performances, Vermont, [1990-1991]; 265653 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Solo Violin Performances, [1980-1994]; 265654 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Solo Violin Performances, [1980-1990]; 265656 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Visual Artists, [1980-1997]; 265658 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Subseries B: Photographs, 265659
    Subseries B is comprised of photographs of events, other musicians, and general publicity.
    Folder titles are derived from Malcolm Goldstein's labels and have been arranged alphabetically.
    - Event Photographs: "Espace Ouvert - Portraits of Malcolm Goldstein" Film by Thierry Collins, 2005-2006; 265680 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Event Photographs: Festival Densites [Barre Philips and Theo Jarrier], 2004; 265681 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Event Photographs: John Cage Music Festival, Germany [photographs by Manfred Leve], May 30, 2002; 265682 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Event Photographs: Leroi Jenksins with Malcolm Goldstein, Montreal [photographs by Herb Greenslade], January 19, 2005; 265683 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Event Photographs: Modern Dance School, Amsterdam, 1982; 265684 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Other Musicians: Cage, John, 1970; 1987; 1993; 265685 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Other Musicians: Celli, Joseph, 1980; 1990; 265686 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Other Musicians: Corner, Philip, 1978; 1981; [undated]; 265687 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Other Musicians: Forti, Simone, May 3, 1989; 265688 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Other Musicians: Knowles, Alison, 1977-1978; 1980; 265689 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Other Musicians: Paik, Nam Jun, 1987; 265690 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Other Musicians: Yoray, Alma [dance], [undated]; 265691 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Publicity and Performance Photographs [1 of 3], [1965-2009]; 265692 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Publicity and Performance Photographs [2 of 3], [undated]; 265693 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Publicity and Performance Photographs [3 of 3], [1964-1998]; 265694 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Publicity Portraits [photographs by Silvia Otte, Yosha Goldstein, Antaramian, Bill Hellerman], [undated]; 265695 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Publicity Portraits [photographs by Silvia Otte], 1994; 265696 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Subseries C: Ephemera, 265697
    Subseries C is comprised of posters, concert programs, announcements, and invitations.
    Materials are arranged chronologically by year range as transcribed from Malcolm Goldstein's labels. Additional information on a selection of materials has been provided in square brackets.
    - 1951-1951: 'Musical Notes' Stuyvesant High School [with photographs], December 14, 1951; May 23, 1952; 265698 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - 1957-1960: [Columbia Composers], 265699 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - 1960-1962: ["The Lamentations of Jeramiah"], 265700 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - 1962-1968: [Columbia Composers; The Bridge Theater][1 of 2], 265701 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - 1962-1968: [Columbia Composers; Judson Church; Dance Circle Company] [2 of 2], 265702 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - 1963-1964: Judson Dance Theater, 265703 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - 1964-1967: [Angry Arts; Avant Garde Festival; "The Lamentations of Jeremiah"; "Ludlow Blues"; "Majority"], 265704 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - 1964-1967: [Tone Roads; New Music at the Bridge], 265705 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - 1965: The Dramatic Arts Center presents "Once", Ann Arbor, Michigan, 265706 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - 1965: "A Concert for Edgard Varese", 265707 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - 1965-1968: [New Music at the Bridge; Angry Arts; Avant Garde Festival; Tone Roads], 265710 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - 1969-1971: ["Tone Roads"; "Dickinson College"][1 of 2], 265711 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - 1969-1971: ["Tone Roads"; "Dickinson College"][2 of 2], 265742 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - 1972-1974: [New Roots in Music and Dance; Goddard College] [1 of 2], 265743 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - 1972-1974: [New Roots in Music and Dance; Intermedia Foundation; Judson Memorial Church; Onion River Arts Council][2 of 2], 265744 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - 1975-1978: New Music Ensemble [1 of 2], 265745 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - 1975-1978: New Music Ensemble [2 of 2], 265746 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - 1975-1978: The Dartmouth Collegium Musicum, 265747 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - 1976: ["Organic Oboe"; Franklin Furnace; The Kitchen], 265748 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - 1976: The Dartmouth Collegium Musicum and New Music Ensemble [1 of 2], 265749 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - 1976: The Dartmouth Collegium Musicum and New Music Ensemble [2 of 2], 265750 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - 1978: Europe Tour, 265751 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - 1978: [Bowdoin College; The Kitchen Center; Washington Square Church], Fall, 1978; 265752 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - 1978: [Bowdoin College; The Kitchen Center; "Flux Concert"], Fall, 1978; 265753 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - 1979: New Music at the Kitchen Center, NY, June 8-16, 1979; 265754 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - 1979: [RAW August Jazz; Avant Garde Festival; New Music America; Pauline Oliveros][1 of 2], 265755 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - 1979: [Dance Theater Workshop; Intermedia Foundation; SUNY Buffalo][2 of 2], 265756 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - 1980: [Art Series Program; Bowdoin College; Alison Knowles][1 of2], Fall, 1980; 265757 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - 1980: ["Soundings"; Michael Byron; Internationales Musikfestival Wien][2 of2], Fall, 1980; 265758 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - 1981: Concert Tour of Europe with Philip Corner, May-June, 1981; 265759 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - 1981: Tour of California [1 of 2], February, 1981; 265761 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - 1981: Tour of California [2 of 2], February, 1981; 265762 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - 1981: Tour of California, Fall, 1981; 265763 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - 1981: [Ear It Live; Parallelogramme][1 of 2], Fall, 1981; 265764 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - 1981: [Alternative Museum; Marin's Song, Illuminated][2 of 2], Fall, 1981; 265767 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - 1982-1983: [Mac Low Retrospective; Roulette; Real Art Ways; Aquinas][1 of 2], Fall, 1982-Spring, 1983; 265770 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - 1982-1983: [Mac Low Retrospective; Newton Arts Center New Music Festival; Real Art Ways; Tone Roads West][2 of 2], Fall, 1982-Spring, 1983; 265780 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - 1982: Austria Tour, May, 1982; 266182 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - 1982: [The Saw Gallery; Palomar College; Steirscher Herbst], Spring, 1982; 266183 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - 1983: Europe Tour with David Moss and Joseph Celli, April-May, 1983; 266184 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - 1983-1984: [Morgan O'Hara; The Bowery Ensemble; New Music America], Summer, 1983- Summer, 1984; 266186 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - 1983-1984: [Real Art Ways; The Bowery Ensemble; Pauline Oliveros], Summer, 1983-Summer, 1984; 266187 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - 1983: Steirischer Herbst, September-October, 1983; 266188 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - 1984: Relache, June, 1984; 266189 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - 1984-1985: ["Soundings"; Pauline Oliveros; David Moss], Fall, 1984- Summer, 1985; 266190 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - 1984-1985: ["Soundings for Solo Violin"; North American New Music Festival; Robert Black], Fall, 1984- Summer, 1985; 266191 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - 1985: [Horspiel; "Certain Rituals"][1 of 2], Fall, 1985; 266192 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - 1985: [Birthday Concert; Composer's Concert; New Music America][2 of 2], Fall, 1985; [1986]; 266193 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - 1985-1986: Pro Musica Nova, Fall, 1985- 1986; 266208 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - 1985-1986: ["On New Music"], 266209 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - 1985-1986: "The Seasons: Vermont", 266210 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - 1986: [Jin Hi Kim; Nanette Domingos; Mobius Sound Art Festival], Fall, 1986; 266194 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - 1986: [Sundays at Cornish; Simone Forti], Fall, 1986; 266195 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - 1987: [John Cage Celebration; "State of the Nation, revisited"; "The Edges of Sound Within"][1 of 2], Fall, 1987; 266196 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - 1987: ["3 Views of Immobility"; Susan Ogberg; Basel; "Gageego"][2 of 2], Fall, 1987; 266201 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - 1988: [John Bergamo; Jim Tenney; Ear to the Ground Festival; Carolee Schneeman], Fall, 1988; 266211 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - 1988: [Documenta 8; Inventionen; Stone Wall Fragments][1 of 2], Fall, 1988; 266212 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - 1988: [Soundscapes; Susan Osberg][2 of 2], Fall, 1988; 266213 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - 1989: ["Sounding the Fragility of Line"; Heidelberger Festival; Workshop Ensemble], Fall, 1989; 266214 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - 1989: [Lake Forest College; Bridging the Gap; 2nd Acustica International Sound Art Festival], Fall, 1989; 266215 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - 1990: [Potluck Performances; Breaking the Shell; Susan Osberg], Summer, 1990; 266217 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - 1990: [Europe Tour], Summer, 1990; 266218 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - 1991-1992: ["October Meeting"; "New From Abroad"][1 of 3], Autumn, 1991- Summer, 1992; 266447 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - 1991-1992: ["The Seasons: Vermont"][2 of 3], Autumn, 1991- Summer, 1992; 266448 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - 1991-1992: Europe Tour [3 of 3], Autumn, 1991- Summer, 1992; 266449 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - 1992-1994: [Europe Tour; John Cage Projekt; Potluck Performances][1 of 3], Autumn 1992- Spring, 1994; 266450 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - 1992-1994: [Decapo Nacht; Radio Bremen; Dorethea Rust][2 of 3], Autumn, 1992- Spring, 1994; 266451 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - 1992-1994: ["Die Reise des Sptazen"; Sound Culture Japan; Critical Band Presents; Cornish Series][3 of 3], Autumn, 1992-Spring, 1994; 266452 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - 1994-1996: Europe Tour [1 of 2], Autumn, 1994- Spring, 1996; 266453 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - 1994-1996: Europe Tour [2 of 2], Autumn, 1994- Spring, 1996; 266454 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - 1996-1998: Europe Tour [1 of 4], Autumn, 1996- Spring, 1998; 266455 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - 1996-1998: [Gustavo Matamoros; A Concert of World Premier Performances] [2 of 4], Autumn, 1996- Spring, 1998; 266456 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - 1996-1998: Europe Tour [3 of 4], Autumn, 1996- Spring, 1998; 266457 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - 1996-1998: Europe Tour [L'Art Pour L'Art; Array Music][4 of 4], Autumn, 1996- Spring, 1998; 266459 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - 1998: [Sound Symposium; Once; Merce Cunningham], 266460 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - 1999: [Trio Diritto; Noise at the Library; L'Art Pour L'Art], 266461 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - 2000: [California Ear Unit; "Uber Land Unter"; Anton Lukoszevieze][1 of 2], 266462 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - 2000: [Relache; Sonorous Processes][2 of 2], 266464 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - 2001: [Matthias Kaul; Quatuor Bozzini][1 of 2], 266465 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - 2001-2002: [Masashi Harada; Cube South Loop Festival; "Bataille"; Quatuor Bozzini][2 of 2], 266467 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - 2003: Suoni di il Popolo Festival of Improvised Music, June 18, 2003; 266468 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - 2003: [New Music Festival of Western Illinois University; Mobius 25; 7th Annual International Festival of Electroacoustic Music], 266469 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - 2004: [Suoni Pe Il Popolo; "Hardscrabble Songs"; "Regarding the Tower of Babel"], 266470 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - 2004: Maerz Musik/ Berliner Festspiele, March, 2004; 266471 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - 2005: [Now Jazz Summit; International Tagung fur Improvisation], 266472 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - 2006: Europe Spring Tour [Dialogue Spiel; Wiener Konzerthaus], 266473 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - 2006: [Europe Tour; Tribute to Jackson Mac Low], 266474 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - 2007: [Europe Tour; "Fragments of the Wall"], 266475 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - 2008: [Europe Tour; Matthias Kaul; Quatuor Bozzini][1 of 2], 266477 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - 2008: [Europe Tour; "espace ouvert"; Festival 4020][2 of 2], 266478 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - 2009: [Europe Tour], 266479 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - 2009: [Europe Tour- Autumn], Autumn, 2009; 266480 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - 2010: [Dorethea Rust; "L'Oubli de L'air"; A Sanctuary for the Arts: Judson Memorial Church and the Avant Garde], 266482 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - 2013: Festival Montreal [Malcom Goldstein and Ratchet Orchestra], 276315 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - 2014-2016: Programs and Announcements (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Interview Transcript and Article Re: Goldstein, 2016-2017 (Box 51, Folder 2-3)
    - 2017-2018: Concert Programs and Workshop Information (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Series IV: Administrative, 266484
  Series IV comprises administrative materials reflecting organization of concert curations, contracts, grants, music production, and teaching materials. Two longer pieces written about Malcolm Goldstein's work are listed under Criticism.
  Material is arranged alphabetically under the general category in which it was grouped upon arrival. Additional Information has been added for clarification and is in square brackets.
  - Application for permanent residence in Canada with support letters from James Tenney and Christian Wolff, February 15, 1991; 266507 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - [Concert Curation]: Mobius Music, [1984]; 266508 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - [Concert Curation]: Tone Roads [announcement flier], 1967; 266512 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - [Concert Curation]: Tone Roads fliers and programs, [1963-1968]; 266513 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - [Concert Curation]: Tone Roads programs and clippings, 1963-1969; 266509 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - [Concert Curation]: Tone Roads proposal and correspondence, October 31, 1962; November 12, 1963; 266510 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - [Concert Curation]: Tone Roads proposal for a center for contemporary music at the New School [Philip Corner, James Tenney], January, 1967; 266514 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - [Concert Curation]: Tone Roads proposal and program notes, February 23, 1965; January, 1967; [undated]; 266511 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Contracts: [1981-1983] recording and publishing company with scores on loan, 266515 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Contracts: 1984-1985 concerts and correspondence, 266516 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Contracts: 1985-1986 concerts, 266517 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Contracts: 1986-1987 concerts, 1988-1990; 266518 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Contracts: 1988-1990 concerts, 266519 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Contracts: [1993-1996] concerts and works on consignment [1 of 2], 266520 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Contracts: [1994-2005] concerts and works on consignment [2 of 2], 266521 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Contracts: "La Souffle du Coyote" performance rights, 1995-1996; 266522 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Contracts: Music publication [1 of 3], [1981-2011]; 266523 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Contracts: Music publication [2 of 3], [1984-1987]; 266524 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Contracts: Music publication [3 of 3], [1984-1995]; 266525 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Contracts: "The Seasons: Vermont" Folkways, [1983-1995]; 266526 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence: CD and LP Projects, [1994-2008]; 266528 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence: Letters to Politicians, [1998-2010]; 266531 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence: Publications and Concert Productions, [1981-2008]; 266527 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Criticism: "I was a music building stowaway: A response to Malcolm Goldstein" by Franetta McMillan, [undated]; 266530 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Criticism: "The Music of Malcolm Goldstein" a Master's Thesis by Jay Michael Arms [annotated by Malcolm Goldstein], December 12, 2012; 266529 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Grants: Awards, [1980-2012]; 266532 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Grants: "Breath-River Route" with Alison Knowles, NEA, [1981-1986]; 266533 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Grants: "Breath-River Route" with Alison Knowles, NEA, 1986; 266534 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Grants: Canada Council for the Arts Shift Festival, November, 2008; 266535 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Grants: "Fragments of the Wall" Conseil des artes et des lettres du Quebec, 2008; 266536 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Grants: National Endowment for the Arts, [1980-1985]; 266537 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Grants: Rockefeller Grant, [1981]; 266538 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Grants: "The Seasons: Vermont" support letters [from John Cage, Christian Wolff, Philip Corner], [1977]; 266539 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Production: Jazz Composers of America- Sales, [1980]; 266540 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Production: "Sounding for Solo Violin" Correspondence, May-June, 1980; 267104 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Production: "Sounding the Full Circle", [June 29, 1989]; 267092 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Production: "Sounding the Full Circle", [1982-1989]; 267093 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Production: "Sounding the Full Circle", [1988-1990]; 267094 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Production: "Sounding the Full Circle", [1988-1989]; 267095 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Production: "Sounding the Full Circle" copyright, [1988-1989]; 267096 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Production: "Sounding the Full Circle" ISBN and Library of Congress, September 5, 1988; 267097 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Production: "Sounding the Full Circle" [mailing lists], November, 1989; 267098 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Production: "Sounding the Full Circle" Permission for reprints, 1983-1988; 267099 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Production: "Sounding the Full Circle" Republication and Reviews, 1989-1990; 267101 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Production: "Sounding the Full Circle" Sales/Distribution, 1989-1992; 267108 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Production: "Sounding the Full Circle" Sales/Distribution, 1989-1992; 267109 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Production: "Sounding the Full Circle" Sales/Distribution, 1989-1992; 267110 (Box 36, Folder 16)